So the stakeholder register, when we
identify our stakeholders, this is the
artifact output that we create the
stakeholder register.
So here's an example of what a stakeholder
register can look like.
So we will contain stakeholder
identification.
What's their name, position, location,
role on the project, if any.
Their assessment information, their
initial needs and expectations,
their possible influence on our project
and stakeholder classification,
whether they're internal, external,
whether they're supporters, neutral,
resistors.
So anything we already
know about the stakeholders
will be listed in that
stakeholder register.
We will update this throughout the project
because stakeholders will come and go.
We'll learn new information about them.
So we will revisit this.
This will be progressively elaborated.
But in initiating in the
very beginning, we need to
try to identify as many
stakeholders as possible.
We'll cover the rest of the processes
coming up.